Be careful where the truth may lead...
Killer Legends is a documentary, history, crime film directed by Joshua Zeman.
Delving into our collective nightmares, this horror-documentary investigates the origins of our
most terrifying urban legends and the true stories that may have inspired them.
Self, played by Rachel Mills.
Self, played by Joshua Zeman.
Peggy Loomis, played by Cindy Butler.
Self, played by Stephen Winick.
Killer Legends is a 2014 American documentary written
and directed by Joshua Zeman for Chiller.
Zeman and Rachel Mills, a researcher, investigate the
real-life origins of several urban legends.
The tone is dark.